João Otávio Dimas Rocha Vianna

May 7th, 1993 – 30 years old Centro – Juiz de Fora – MG – Availability to move and travel (32) 99162-2370

jobs.rochavianna@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/rochavianna/

https://rocha-vianna.github.io/rochavianna.github.io/

GOAL

Data Analyst

PROFESSIONAL RESUME

IT professional with expertise in documentation, creation of procedures and customization of functionalities, focused on databases. Solid skills in SQL, Excel and Power BI, with learning in Python and R. Extraction activities, data modeling and storytelling for dashboards, aiming for insights for data-based decision making.

LANGUAGE

Advanced **English**Native **Portuguese**

ACADEMIC EDUCATION

Database Technologist - Estácio - expected completion date Dec/2023

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

DBS Digital - 03/2021 - at the moment

Mid-sized IT services and consultancy company
Oracle Cloud Developer

- Customization on the Oracle Cloud platform
- Working in Oracle database
- Development of documentation and procedures
- Import and export of massive data

AlmavivA do Brasil - 04/2019 - 03/2021

Multinational IT services and consultancy company Specialized service representative

- Problem solving
- Expertise in customer service via telephone and digital media
- Preparation of spreadsheets and reports

Aue Software - 02/2017 - 08/2017

Small software development company IT Intern

- Development of features for proprietary software
- Carrying out functional tests
- Maintenance of machines, networks and software
- Editing articles for the company blog

COURSES AND QUALIFICATIONS

- Data Analyst Associate DataCamp 2023
- Advanced Excel
- Advanced SQL
- Advanced Power BI